My wife and I manage this pharmacy together. It's a
small town, but the demand for medicines is the same here
too. We manage to fulfill household needs together,
but some of our desires remain
unfulfilled. Sometimes I wish I had another
income. I want to
install a bigger TV, a new refrigerator, and
much more. For all this, I need the
assurance of a plan that will
support you in fulfilling all your responsibilities. A trusted name is ICICI
Prudential Life. We bring to you a
new-age plan, ICICI Prudential Sukh
Samriddhi, which will give you a regular
guaranteed income so that you can fulfill your dreams, big or small.
If you, like Prakash Patil,
want a guaranteed source of income for all your desires, then
ICICI Prudential Sukh Samriddhi's income option
offers you many benefits. If you
pay a premium of Rs. 50,000 every year for 10 years, then
after the premium payment term is over,
you will get a
guaranteed income of Rs. 52,125 every year for the next 8 years.
Apart from this, the policy's majority  But
you will also be given a lump sum amount. You
can use the De-Date feature which will
give you income on a date of your choice. This
policy's Savings Deposit feature gives you the choice
that if you do not need income in any year, you
can deposit that income with us in a savings wallet. This
deposited amount will keep growing and
you can withdraw it anytime. You
can use this feature whenever you want during the policy term
and you are also protected by life cover for the entire policy term.
So now,
like Prakash Patil,
fulfill all your needs with happiness and prosperity from ICICI. Choose
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance.
Your trusted partner in fulfilling every dream of you and your loved ones.
Khuda
[Music]